# **Vilius Andriekus**

Email: ViliusAndriekus@outlook.com | Mobile: 07456754898 | Linked in: Vilius Andriekus | GitHub: FloHolo

## **Personal Statement:**

A proactive and engaged team player, my range of experiences across the hospitality sector has ensured a focus on providing a well-rounded and welcoming environment for clients. I continue to maintain a resilient and persevering attitude to my work.

### **IT Experience:**



<u>University Project for "NHS Family Voice App Design"</u>: Worked in team to create an app for end-of-life support for family. This project included creating: UML class, Sequence and Use Case Diagrams alongside Wireframe, Use case, Requirements list and Legal documents such as Diversity, Legal Compliance, Professional Standard Compliance, Social and Ethics Compliance and Sustainability Statement

<u>Java "Itinerary Manager":</u> Created bookkeeping application to enter future events and calculate the costs for them.

<u>Enterprise Project "QuickCare":</u> Participated in ExpoTees in which we showed the health care app to industry representatives. In this project worked on full-stack development, handled reports and I was a scrum master for the team.

#### **Employment History:**

Pret A Manger – Front of House Supervisor	Sep 2022 – Sep 2023
Costa – Barista Maestro	Sep 2021 – Sep 2022
Young & Co.'s Brewery Plc – Assistant Manager	Jul 2021 – Sep 2021
Monolith (UK) LTD – Warehouse Staff	Oct 2020 – Jun 2021
Pret A Manger – Assistant Manager	Feb 2020 – Sep 2020
EAT. – Assistant Manager	Aug 2017 – Feb 2020
Wrap it Up!	Aug 2016 – Aug 2017

#### **Assistant Manager and Supervisor roles:**

- Widening my understanding of the Commercial retail/hospitality sector while working with a diverse range of clients and colleges
- Managing people, rotas, orders, stock control and banking

## **Education & Qualifications:**

Waltham Forest Sixth Form College, BTEC ICT Extended Diploma  Tauragės "Šaltinio" Progimnazija, (Lithuanian General State Education)  Java programming skills  Intermediate	
Java programming skills  SQL skills  C# programming skills  Python  Intermediate  Intermediate  Beginner	